budgetyourtrip.com 2015-05-04

# Budget Your Trip | Privacy Policy

## Budget Your Trip Privacy Policy

#### Date Last Revised: March 25, 2015

BudgetYourTrip is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information about our users. This Privacy & Security Policy explains how we protect personal information provided through our website www.BudgetYourTrip.com (the "Site") and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the Site (the "Service"). "Personal information" for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you, such as your name or email address.

  1. Your Privacy is not for sale 

Simply put, we do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time. BudgetYourTrip uses and discloses your personal information only as follows:

    * to analyze site usage and improve the Service;
    * to enforce BudgetYourTrip's Terms of Use; and
    * as otherwise set forth in this Privacy and Security Policy.
  2. We limit the collection and use of personal information 

Certain areas and features of BudgetYourTrip.com are available to you without registration or the need to provide to us any information. However, other features of the Site or the Service may require registration, which involves provision to BudgetYourTrip of an email address and a password. 

BudgetYourTrip may make anonymous or aggregate personal information and disclose such data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to:

    * Advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes, such as the number of users who visited a particular region or how many users clicked on a particular BudgetYourTrip Offer;
    * Organizations approved by BudgetYourTrip that conduct research into consumer spending; and
    * Users of the Service for purposes of comparison of their spending relative to the broader community and an estimate of expected spending in an area.
    * Such information does not identify you individually. Access to your Registration Information, Account Information and any other personal information you provide is strictly restricted

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

  3. Changes to your Registration Information 

If your Registration Information changes during your subscription to BudgetYourTrip, you may update it any time via the Service.

  4. Online session information and use is only used to improve your experience 

When you visit BudgetYourTrip.com, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality.

  5. Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, BudgetYourTrip reserves the right (and you authorize BudgetYourTrip) to share or disclose your personal information when BudgetYourTrip determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate:

    * To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the BudgetYourTrip.com Terms of Use;
    * To prevent prohibited or illegal activities; or
    * When required by any applicable law, rule regulation, subpoena or other legal process.
  6. Your data may be transferred upon change of control but only in accordance with this Policy 

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. 

  7. You can transport or delete your data 

Your data is yours. You can remove it anytime you want. When you request us to delete your account for the Service, your data will be permanently expunged from our primary production servers and further access to your account will not be possible. We will also promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your Account Information and delete all account credentials. However, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate data derived from your Account Information, may remain on our production servers indefinitely. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your personal information.
